(Leonard:)I got to tell you, the more
I read about the primordial
(Leonard:)gravity wave discovery,
the more excited I get.
(Raj:)I know. Being an
astrophysicist right now
(Raj:)is like being a rock star.
(Howard:)Only without the sex.
(Raj:)Yeah, literally, none of it.
(Leonard:)What do you think about it, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Meh.
(Raj:)Are you kidding me?
(Raj:)This may be the biggest
scientific breakthrough
(Raj:)of our lifetime.
(Raj:)How can you, as a theoretical
physicist, not care about this?
(Sheldon:)Maybe it's because
I'm not an elitist.
(Sheldon:)How does this gravity wave
breakthrough
(Sheldon:)help the man on the street?
You know?
(Sheldon:)Who's looking out
for Joe Six-Pack
(Sheldon:)and all his quantum physics concerns?
(Leonard:)Oh, my God, you're jealous.
(Sheldon:)Why would I be jealous?
(Leonard:)I don't know. Maybe because
the origin of the universe
(Leonard:)just got proven,
the Higgs field just got proven
(Leonard:)and you've been working on
string theory for the last 20 years
(Leonard:)and you're no closer to proving
it than when you started.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, I've had a lot
on my plate.